Hi, I'm Maya.
嗨，我是瑪雅。
I'm the vice president of strategy, operations and outreach
我是
at Google Research.
Google 研究的策略、營運和外展副總裁。
This means I spend my time
這意味著我花時間
exploring what's on the horizon and helping to make it real.
探索未來的東西，並幫助實現它。
That includes AI. You’re probably already using AI yourself, even if you don't know it.
這包括人工智能。即使您不知道，您可能已經自己已經使用 AI。
It's the technology behind things like giving you optimized traffic routes
這是為您提供最佳化的流量路線
or personalized suggestions for YouTube videos.
或針對 YouTube 視頻的個性化建議等技術背後的技術。
AI is also creating new ways of working or running a business,
AI 也正在創造新的工作或經營業務方
and it has a lot of huge potential for you and your team.
式，它對您和您的團隊具有很大的潛力。
And like any new technology,
就像任何新技術一
it can be intimidating to know where to start or how to keep up,
樣，知道從哪裡開始或如何跟上步伐可能令人恐懼，
especially when it feels like there are new things happening every day.
尤其是當感覺每天都有新事情發生的時候。
Don't worry though.
不過，不用擔心。
We're here to help.
我們在這裡為您提供幫助。
In this course, you'll get AI skills employers are looking for.
在本課程中，您將獲得雇主正在尋找的 AI 技能。
This includes important fundamentals about AI, how to apply AI to your own work,
這包括有關 AI 的重要基礎知識、如何將 AI 應用於自己的工作，
and how to be a responsible AI user.
以及如何成為負責任的 AI 用戶。
These skills will help expand the possibilities
這些技能將有助於擴大您
of what you can do with AI at work.
可以在工作中使用 AI 做的可能性。
We brought in a team of AI experts and practitioners from across
我們將來自
Google to serve as your guides.
Google 各地的 AI 專家和從業人員組成的團隊成為您的指導。
You'll explore different use cases that you can apply to your own work.
您將探索不同的使用案例，可以應用於自己的工作。
We focus on getting you right into the tools.
我們專注於讓您直接使用工具。
That's intentional.
這是故意的。
You will learn how to play the piano without touching the keys. Would you?
您將學習如何在不觸摸鍵的情況下彈鋼琴。你會嗎？
AI is no different.
AI 也沒有什麼不同。
The best way to learn is by doing.
學習的最佳方法是做。
Throughout your learning journey, you'll practice using
在整個學習過程中，您將練習使
AI with access to Google's most capable models.
用 AI，以訪問 Google 最有能力的模型。
You'll start with the Gemini app as your home base.
您將從 Gemini 應用程序作為主基地開始。
You can think of it as your all purpose AI assistant.
您可以將其視為您的多用途 AI 助手。
You can access it from desktop or on a mobile,
您可以從桌面或移動設備訪問它，
and there's all sorts of stuff you could do from this one app.
並且您可以通過此應用程序進行各種操作。
You'll also practice using other AI tools like NotebookLM and AI Studio.
您還將練習使用筆記本 LM 和 AI 工作室等其他 AI 工具。
What are some of the things you'll be able to do after completing this certificate?
完成此證書後，您可以做哪些事情？
You'll learn how to look ahead and anticipate questions someone might ask
您將學習如何展望未來並預測某人在
before a big meeting, or how to understand a topic that's new to you.
大會議之前可能會問的問題，或如何理解對您來說新的主題。
We'll show you how. You'll build project roadmaps, a compelling presentation,
我們將向您展示如何。您將建立專案路線圖、引人注目的演示文稿、
marketing imagery, and charts that tell a story.
行銷圖像以及講述故事的圖表。
You'll see how AI can help turn rough ideas into clear communication
您將了解 AI 如何幫助將粗略
to get your teammates on board, and you'll be able to transform raw data
的想法轉化為清晰的溝通，讓您的團隊成員加入，並且您將能夠將原始數據轉換為
into visuals that everyone on your team can understand.
團隊中所有人都能理解的視覺效果。
By the end, you'll even be able to build your own custom apps
到最後，您甚至可以構建自己的自定義應用程序，例
like an interactive dashboard or a media asset creator,
如交互式儀表板或媒體資產創建器，並且您
and you'll do it by directing AI with natural language.
將通過使用自然語言指導 AI 來完成此操作。
No coding required.
無需編碼。
When you start applying your new AI skills to your day to day work,
當您開始將新的 AI 技能應用於日常工作時，
you'll be able to solve new problems and boost your impact.
您將能夠解決新的問題並提高您的影響力。
After you're done, you'll earn a certificate from Google
完成後，您將獲得 Google
demonstrating skills that employers are looking for,
的證書，展示雇主正在尋找的技能，並且您可以將此憑證添加到您的履歷和 LinkedIn 個人資料中。
You'll also have a portfolio of things you've built yourself using AI.
您還將擁有一系列您使用 AI 自己構建的東西。
So let's get started.
所以讓我們開始吧。